Lupu Anisia Ioana

Java Software Developer

Email: anisia.lupu@yahoo.com Phone: +(40) 748 842 145



Hello, I'm Anisia and I'm a Software Developer.

I have almost 3 years of experiencing in coding, testing and continuosly improving software products.

With a good analytical thinking and a lot of perseverance I accepted the challenge to make the world a better place in the era of digitalization.

Skills: Java , J2EE , SQL , Hibernate , Spring , Clean Code , Commitment , Teamwork , Curiosity

Languages: Romanian, English

Experience

Unicredit Services

Junior Java Developer

Jun 2018 - Present

- Technologies:

Apr 2017 - Jun 2018

- Technologies:

Java 7

Primefaces

SQL, DB2



Java2EE

Hibernate

JUnit, Mockito

Being part of the "Innovation Team", in order to deliver solutions that increase the quality of our development workflow and products, I worked on building an automation testing framework from scratch for two web applications in our department.

- · Propose technologies for developing/improving the framework;
- Introduce the BDD approach in order to encourage collaboration among developers and non-technical participants
- · Write and configure automation tests suites
- · Participate in daily scrum meetings
- Assist testers colleagues to write automation tests and understand the framework
- · Writing technical documentation

Develop new features and fix existing issues for a financial advisory application which provides professional expertise in investing/desinvesting on financial instruments depending on the user target profile.

- · Provide application development and testing
- · Debugging, finding and fixing bugs
- Participate in daily scrum meetings
- Implementing unit tests for new features
- · Communicating with testers and business analysts
- Code review

Centric

Database and Application
Development Internship

Maven Git, Gitlab

Aug 2015 - Nov 2015 (Internship 3 Months)

- Tech Stack:

SQL	PL/SQL	Oracle
Oracle Forms		

Involved in a summer full-time internship in which I developed a custom desktop application using Oracle PL/SQL and Oracle Forms.

Education

2016 - 2018 Master in Software Systems Engineering

Faculty of Computer Science, "Alexandru Ioan Cuza" University of Iași

laşi

2013 - 2016 Bachelor's Degree in Computer Science

Faculty of Computer Science, "Alexandru Ioan Cuza" University of Iași

laşi

2019 - 2013 High School Diploma

"Petru Rareș" National College

Piatra-Neamţ (hometown)

Hobbies:

Traveling Swimming

Reading

Loving animals